# LEAH BANKS

□ leahb\_96@hotmail.co.uk
□ 07939 263 330
□ London

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/leahrbanks">https://www.linkedin.com/in/leahrbanks</a> https://github.com/leahbanks

## PROFILE

I am an adaptable, logical thinker with a keen interest in how technology can create a positive impact. With a background in Customer Happiness and the arts, I have recently completed a 13 week full-time accelerated bootcamp in Software Development - a field that combines my professional knowledge of user experience, with my passion for creative problem solving and my desire for accessibility and inclusivity within the world of tech and beyond.

\_\_\_\_\_

## SKILLS

Language: Javascript

Front End: React.js, React Native, HTML5, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Document Object Model (DOM)

Back End: Express.js, PostgreSQL, Test Driven Development (TDD), REST APIs, Node.js, OAuth

Testing: Jest, SuperTest

Applications/Version Control: Git, Trello,

Atlassian, Jira

## EDUCATION

**University of Westminster** 2015 - 2018

**Fine Art Mixed Media** First Class Honours

**Walsall College** 2013 - 2014

Diploma in Foundation Studies in Art & Design Merit

**Heath Park School** 2011 - 2013

A Level Art & Design CAS Level English Language & Literature В

**AS Level Psychology** 

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- · Between September and November 2022, I undertook a career transition and self-taught basic Javascript in order to kickstart my career in Software Development.
- · Between December 2017 and June 2018, I took a career break to focus on my final-year studies.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Trainee Full Stack Developer

**Northcoders** 

November 2022 - March 2023

- Pair programming
- Writing production-ready code using front-end and back-end frameworks:
  - Creating web applications using React and React Router
  - Using PostgreSQL to create and seed databases
  - Creating server endpoints using Express.js
  - Utilising Git for version control best practice

NC News - Back End Project

NC News - Front End Project

# **Customer Happiness Team Leader**

Oddbox

April 2022 - September 2022

- · Managed and supported a team of 6 agents to meet weekly KPI targets, holding fortnightly and quarterly reviews
- · Proactively handled any issues that arose, alerting and working with the relevant teams to implement solutions and minimise impact on the customer
- Worked closely with the Tech team to manage the website's AI Chat Bot and optimise its performance
- · Worked closely with the Product team to relay feedback on the website, test new functionality and inform decisions on the user journey during the migration to a new subscription management system

## **Customer Happiness Executive**

Oddbox

November 2022 - April 2022

- Addressed customer complaints and queries with efficiency and empathy
- Regularly surpassed weekly KPI targets (200 tickets solved)
- Managed and updated online FAQs to improve user experience and streamline customer contact
- Safely managed customer data to conform to GDPR guidance
- Worked collaboratively with other teams using systems such as ReTool, Atlassian and Jira

# **Visitor Experience Assistant**

Serpentine Galleries

April 2019 - November 2020

- · Acted as a first point of contact for all visitors and internal staff
- Collected and documented visitor feedback to improve service
- Visual Merchandising

### Gallery Host

Serpentine Galleries

June 2018 - April 2019

### **Customer Service Assistant**

Tesco

June 2016 - December 2017

Further work experience is available upon request.